tiptopjob.com 2009-06-16

# Privacy

| Back to Footer Topics Section Index  
---  
|  |   
---|---  
  
|  These Privacy Conditions are the basis for individuals, Clients and Agencies using any of the **TipTopJob** web sites. which include the .com or country domains, and particularly this site - **TipTopJob.com.

TipTopJob 

**will make every effort to comply with the obligations under the UK 1998 Data Protection Act. Our privacy policy details the ways we collect and protect your personal information. **TipTopJob** is committed to protecting the privacy of those using our website and the confidentiality of any personal information with which subscribers provide us. This privacy policy does not cover links within this site to other websites or third party suppliers. We understand that the information you or your agent provides on the database is confidential and we will use our best endeavour in maintaining it.   
---  
**There are currently 3 ways in which we collect personal information**

**\- Information and Service Requests**  
If you request information or a service via email, letter or telephone, we may need your personal details to process that request.

**\- Online Forms**  
There is a range of online forms to allow you to make comments or request particular services. Each form requests your contact details, however you are only obliged to provide particular details if it is marked as mandatory; indicated by an asterisk *. If you do provide personal information we will use it only to process your request and, thereafter in accordance with the individual (see below) registrations for the services provided. 

**\- Session Cookies**  
A cookie is a small piece of information about an Internet session that may be created when a visitor accesses a web site. Cookies store information about your use of **TipTopJob** website on your computer. It is sent by a web site to store on your computer where it can be retrieved by the web site at a later time. Cookies help make your web experience more personalised and convenient. They also protect registered usernames and passwords and advertisers on the site use the cookies to target their advertisements more directly. If you use the "Download or Request by Post" Online Forms in the site and request that information is sent out by post, you will have to provide a contact name and address. If you do so, a "session cookie" will be created and your contact details will be stored in a temporarily file on your computer for the duration of your visit to the site. If you then wish to request that another document be posted out to you, your contact details will already be there. You can set your computer not to accept cookies.  
  
## DATA PROTECTION

**TipTopJob** is registered under the Data Protection Act, 1998 and at all times use best endeavours to comply with the terms of the Act in all our dealings with your personal data. 

  * We will never sell personal information or share personal information with third parties without your explicit consent. 
  * If you provide us with personal information as part of an information or service request through this website, we will only use your data to process your request (subject to the data protection registration for the individual service concerned). 
  * In processing any requests we may have to pass it to another department or agency within the group.

**TipTopJob** Data Protection Registrations can be viewed at the [ Information Commissioner's](http://www.dataprotection.gov.uk/) website, by clicking on this link.

Our use of personal information and Photos supplied by users of this site is governed by the privacy policy. Information provided by third parties are taken in good faith and may be used but with the option available for Users to set themselves to opt out of their use on parts of the system.

I confirm that, to the best of my knowledge, the information I have registered is correct and that I have registered/re-registered of my own free will. By submitting my details I agree that the information given may be used for registration and purposes associated with finding me employment and may be passed on to relevant third parties as covered under the UK Data Protection Act.   
  
##  VEHICLE & PHOTO INFORMATION

You will be requested for a series of information for us to hold and use on the site. This will contain your Name and contact information, categories, email alert categories, your Vehicle details and Photos, which can be uploaded. Your information, or selected parts of the information, will be made available to be viewed and downloaded, by way of an online search over the Internet, by Vehicle Buyers. These may be direct Buyers, Trade Buyers or other organisations, which pay for the service.  

## IMPORTANT

**TipTopJob** cannot restrict the Clients, Agencies, or Buyers that access items on our database and cannot be held responsible for any eventuality. You can choose to opt in and out of making your information available depending on your requirements from time to time. Clients will be located in countries from all round the world and especially outside the European Union. The option is available for anyone to switch to different **TipTopJob** sites but still request data from whatever country they desire. 

When you register with **TipTopJob** , you will first register and provide a User Key and password. You will create your own Profile and upload one or more items and we will store the information on our databases. You can update or delete any of the information at any time. It is your responsibility to ensure that your Item Details and contact details are kept up to date. Once your User Profile and Items are on our database, we will contact you periodically by email to request whether you want to remain active or inactive. By being set inactive, it stops your Item Details being searched and will be archived until you wish to make it active again. We have the right that if we do not have a positive response to a series of emails, we will remove your information from the database.  
  
## PASSWORDS

Passwords are for the sole use of the person to whom they are issued. We may deny access to a password if we reasonably believe that an unauthorised person is using it or that the user is breaching these terms and conditions.  

## STATISTICS

We provide statistics about site visitors and users to others, such as, the number of visitors to the site, the number of different Items on the site and the number registered. This information is provided to third parties, clients, customers, advertisers and suppliers but this will not disclose the identity of individuals.   

## SECURITY

Our site is protected against unauthorised access using the latest security devices and 'firewalls'.   

## LINKING TO TipTopJob

You do not need our permission to link to **TipTopJob** and we do not object to you linking directly to any page on the site. However, you must set such links to open in the entire browser window, preferably as a new window, and not within frames contained in your own site. 

If you would like to arrange for a mutual link to be set up from our site to yours, please email or phone us, using the details in [Contact Us](http://www.tiptopjob.com/displaycontent/sectionid/16/contentid/80_contact_us) **[  
](http://www.aicr.org.uk/)**  
  
## SUBJECT ACCESS 

Under the Data Protection Act, you are entitled to make a subject access request to see information we hold about you. There is a charge of £12.00 for this service.[ ](http://www.healthcarejobbank.com/)  

## FURTHER INFORMATION

Use the "Contact Us" details if you have a question or need further information about **TipTopJob** data protection obligations. Alternatively, [ click here](http://www.dataprotection.gov.uk/), for more general information.

You may also find our [Terms and Conditions Page](http://www.tiptopjob.com/displaycontent/sectionid/16/contentid/168_terms_conditions) page of interest.  

Share It / Bookmark It :  **Privacy**

Back to Footer Topics Section Index
